Hey! Youpi!
-[Menthuthuyoupi] Hmm?
-[Shoot gasps]
[Knuckle] Over here, you bastard!
Works for me.
That'll distract Youpi,
and, if we're lucky,
it might even
be enough to save Shoot.
[opening theme music playing]
[singer singing in Japanese]
[singer singing in English]
DUTY X AND X QUESTION
that the name he had spoken
with such confidence
had aroused Welfin
and Bloster's suspicions
as he headed
deep beneath the palace
to continue his search for Palm.
[elevator dings]
that he would not leave
the palace without finding her.
[Ikalgo] Palm is a friend
of my friends,
and I will rescue her.
Any friend of theirs
is a friend of mine!
[dramatic music playing]
[narrator] The very fact
that Palm was risking her life
because I decided that I would.
it would automatically go back up.
To ascend from the basement,
only one person at a time
could use the elevator,
and on top of that,
a specific code had to be entered.
an alarm would sound,
and the doors would lock.
-Entering the wrong code three times…
-[elevator dings]
would alert security
and release sleeping gas.
The violator would then be captured.
In other words,
an error meant death.
[panel buzzes]
[narrator] Both the violator
and the code's original owner
would be killed,
making one's personal entry code
as valuable as one's own life.
The only people whose codes
allow them to use the elevator
without these restrictions
And it was easier
to use this elevator
than the freight entrance,
[elevator dings]
[Welfin] What is that smell?
What's wrong with Flutter?
Yeah, that's Blo, all right.
I can tell by the scent.
but it's faint.
[narrator] The stench
of Flutter's decomposing body
dulled Welfin's sense of smell.
[Welfin] Blo followed Flutter
when he went underground,
so when Flutter said, "Hagya,"
there's no way he didn't notice it.
Unless Bloster's in on it, too.
I was keeping a close eye
on the intruder,
If he was and if he's working
with the intruder,
-[gasps]
-[gunfire]
So he could ambush me downstairs!
Damn it!
[panting]
Damn it. This is my chance.
Flutter is clearly acting suspiciously.
If I can just set him up
as the perp of the bomb threat,
I can prove to Bizeff
how valuable I am.
Bizeff!
Forget Flutter.
First, I need to find Bizeff.
If you'll both excuse me,
my job here is done.
Killua, when you get inside,
you make the call.
"Make the call"?
and disappeared into the darkness.
[suspenseful music playing]
Meleoron and Shoot
could only hold their breaths
and brace for what would come.
Bring it on!
I get it now.
So this thing is yours, huh?
It is time now.
You have accrued interest.
Hmm?
So the number went up, did it?
[suspenseful music playing]
[grunts]
[growls]
[gasps]
I guess my attacks
don't affect it at all.
What is that damn thing?
[chuckles]
Don't run away!
Answer me! What is this?
You really think I'd tell you,
you son of a bitch!
If you wanna know,
you gotta catch me!
[Meleoron] Damn!
Knuckle's planning
to fight Youpi alone,
and I can't get to him,
not through that deadly,
sword-like onslaught.
There's no way!
[groans]
If I do,
then Hotel Rafflesia
will cease to function.
Any minor wound, any injury…
will surely not be in vain.
keep going.
[Meleoron] I can't…
say it!
I can't tell Shoot to give his all,
'cause he already is.
no matter how much I want to.
Come on, Shoot!
You have to survive!
Please don't die!
No one's here.
Don't panic.
Look around carefully.
If I'm found out, I could
still pass as one of the ants.
Except,
depending on who I run into,
Okay, activate.
There, that's Morel's Smoky Jail,
which means that Morel and Pouf
are facing off one-on-one
in the throne room.
That only leaves two,
Gon and Killua.
[gasps]
[tense music playing]
Welfin?
Oh, no! He's trouble!
Out of all the Squadron Leaders,
he's the biggest skeptic.
Once he suspects you,
he won't trust you again
till you're dead!
[Welfin sniffing]
Which way do I go?
[continues sniffing]
What if he goes the same way?
What if I can't hold
my breath that long?
I'm at my limit!
[groans]
I gotta exhale and inhale
in one fast move.
[exhales]
Huh?
[Meleoron]
And now inhale. Activate!
[gasping]
An enemy?
[narrator] Welfin's ability
reflected his guarded,
I'm gonna count to three.
You better show yourself.
And if you don't,
I'll tear you to pieces!
[growls]
One…
two…
three!
[powering up]
[narrator] To use Missileman,
Welfin chooses his target.
Had Meleoron
stayed in the same place,
Welfin's attack would certainly
have reached its target,
whether Welfin
could sense him or not.
But because the criteria
were not met, it misfired.
Once activated,
Missileman will pursue its target
until it hits its mark.
No one can sustain the impact
and survive.
He was even suspicious
of his own ability.
He only thought
of Missileman as a tool
to give him leverage in negotiations.
would have more worries
than he could tolerate.
Someone was here. I'm sure of it.
The fact that they're using
that kind of deodorant
proves that they know
about my nose.
That means there are traitors
among us.
There's no doubt about it.
So there are others besides Flutter?
There would almost have to be.
What's more,
it's gotta be someone I know.
That's why they're hiding their scent.
'Cause they can kill me
whenever they want?
really the right thing to do?
[triumph music playing]
Gon and Killua
had finally found their target,
a Royal Guard by the name of Neferpitou,
and continued their quest to avenge Kite.
[closing theme music playing]
[Gon] Killua.
[both] No matter what, don't lose hope!
[singer singing in Japanese]